toprankers.com 2015-11-17

# Top Rankers

Your privacy is important to us and we, at TopRankers respect the need to protect your private information. We understand the sensitivity of the personal information which may concern such diverse fields ranging from your career aspirations to your gender preferences. We shall take such reasonable steps as may be necessary to ensure that your private information remains confidential. 

## Information collected by TopRankers

  * You have total control on the privacy of your information
  * Your information will never be sold, exchanged or disclosed to any third party for marketing purposes
  * You can decide whether you want to opt-in to receive offers from us

You can browse our website without registration. We may collect and store the information that you voluntarily disclose to us, in order to access our free tests and discussion forum. We do not share your personal information with any third party. We do not collect information about our visitors from email databases, private/ public organization or bodies. 

We may use your information to contact you via email or telephone, typically to get feedback, to inform you about new products or provide support on your issues. If you do not want us to contact you via email, you can unsubscribe at any time. 

When you purchase our online products or register for classroom training, you need to make the payment online, thus you will be required to share your personal information such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, address(s), credit card number, expiration, and CVV number, with us. During this program, we store your contact information in our registration and order-entry systems. Your credit card information is never stored in our system as it is processed by our payment gateway which uses Secure Encryption Technology (SSL). 

## Cookie Information

In order to enhance your online experience and track website performance, our website uses cookies. It’s a small text file which gets placed in your computer hard drive and can be retrieved later. 

## External Links

Our website may have links to other sites which includes third party websites or resources. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and information practices of third party websites. Please read privacy policies of third party websites as every website has different terms of use and privacy policies. 

## Copyright information

You can electronically copy or take print of the website pages, if it is being used for personal use only. TopRankers holds the copyright to all the material on this website, unless otherwise indicated. A written permission of the copyright holder must be obtained for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law. 

## Sharing your personal information

If you have purchased a TopRankers course, we may ask you for testimonial and if you authorize us, we will display your testimonial on our website, photos and videos or in our social media channels such as Facebook, YouTube etc. You should be aware that your publicly identifiable information could be used to send you promotional, unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for your personal information which you have chosen to display. 

If you don’t want us to feature your pictures/testimonials on our website or on our social media channels, you can write a mail to [info@toprankers.com](mailto:info@toprankers.com)

## Personal Information Corrections

You can contact us if you notice that the information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete. Please send us a mail to [info@toprankers.com](mailto:info@toprankers.com)

## Changes to Privacy Policy

This privacy policy terms may change time to time and we reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we update the privacy policy, all our registered users will be notified via email. 

## Privacy Policy Questions

If you have any questions regarding Privacy Policy, Please write to [info@toprankers.com](mailto:info@toprankers.com)
